{"data":[{"question":"Many universities, school classes taught in English even though the native language is not English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"myself","b":"the","c":"rapidity","d":"cheap","answer":"3","explain":"- Rapidity-> rapid","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I myself prefer the underground as it is rapidity, easy and cheap.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"such","b":"in","c":"that","d":"without","answer":"1","explain":"- Such-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"There are such many cars and buses in London that one can not drive along the roads quickly, and without many stops.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"don't","c":"good","d":"to find","answer":"3","explain":"- Good-> well","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"If you don't know London very good, it is very difficult to find the bus you want.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Some","b":"flies","c":"more than","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Flies-> fly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Some butterflies flies more than 3000 kilometers on their journey to the south.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"On","b":"wintering","c":"of","d":"like","answer":"1","explain":"- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"On the wintering places, millions of butterflies cover the trees and ground like a carpet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"certainly","b":"average","c":"has","d":"that","answer":"4","explain":"- That-> than","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"It is certainly true that the average woman has weaker muscles that the average man.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"lived","b":"hunt","c":"strength","d":"most","answer":"2","explain":"- Hunt-> hunted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"When men lived in caves and hunt animals for food, strength of body was the most important thing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"same","c":"any","d":"do","answer":"3","explain":"- Any-> some","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of the words are the same in American and in British English, but the American people say any English words not like people do in England.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"much","c":"because","d":"also","answer":"2","explain":"- Much-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"In Canada much people speak English because they also came from England many years ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"at","b":"has","c":"starts","d":"works","answer":"4","explain":"- Works-> working","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}